[Music]
Policy Tradition
So Shall We
Note Start Key
Other Policy
Give What Do You Do I Be
Greedy Key Respect So Be Fine
Art
Iastic
Help In Way And Her Find Five And Plus One
D From Policy You Can Watch
And Usually Conversion
Match Fast Policy
Implementation Policy Impression Date D
Recipes
Selection Arty Sorry
In D System Of Equations I Can Just Take
D Invert
Matrix And If You Like It If I Jump Do
D Iterative Fashion Just Like You Did In
Validation In Sub Iterating On L I Can It
Right On
Stopping Criteria But I
Can Do This Here Well Next Think Is
Policy
Policy Improvement Okay It's An Second
Step Is Called Policy Valuation Third
Step Is Called Policy Improvement
Way Maxis Give Component Wise Forever
State Yes You Know D Max
Bikini
Date Because I'm
Checking On Equality
Stopping Right So Yer Jump B Multiple
Actions Date Give You D Max
Hairs And Actions On Giving  n max right
pain giver is this some action your choice in d
policy per n state this state n + 1 if
d from action belongs to d max set you
bill pick action
from d max set
suppose going up and going right right
in d previous going up per this state
five star
you
easy
stopping condition holds can i see wifi
and sold b 5 star
right so dat mains value functions
right so tha mains date mains its c optical
function
[music]
welcome change because
generating her right it means so
soft value function has and change and this is
essentially this part of it is essentially
l operating on v5
so tha essentially means the automatically
show that happens when they have to show that
policy are
spy and plus
policy it's same as this give dat bill give d from
answer bill be greater because this is obtend
in maxing this expression right
this expression and maximizing it and
whatever gives me  d maximum I am saying
he and plus one right so this is d
maximum on d left hand side so d
maximum hasti b greater than equal to you
whatever value bill get me palgi in some mother
pi and her
this is clear right because
this is actually equal so were equal as so that in this is what right so everything okay so d
last beat they need is you show date
d only fine it number
okay component voice so every component of we is
greater than sorry I didn't define it really I should have so this
essential way n
plus one of s1 is greater than equal to you b
and of s1 office you on s3 who's
well
climbing you cummings so that so I stop
they can come out and they can ask questions
[music]
[applause]